If you want to be a better critical thinker and debater, which we absolutely need right
now, read these books.
To the love of God, learn how to read a fucking book.
This book, How to Read a Book, is an incredible introduction in how to properly analyze and
understand the argument within a book.
One of my personal favorites, which is an incredible introduction to logic, is the power
of logic.
We're going to learn how to spot fallacies, how to actually make an argument the difference
between an inductive argument and a deductive argument, and so much more.
If we're arguing, we're going to teach you how to debate, how to spot fallacies, how
to stand your ground, and so much more.